we get pennies they come for our
мы получаем копейки они приходят за наши
money here they get high rowdy anything
же бабки здесь кайфуют дебошир всё что
you want you touch them with a finger they immediately run to
хочешь пальцем их тронешь сразу бегут в
the police let’s speak normally right away
полицию давайте нормально говорить сразу
just because all the young people here are
только потому что тут все молодёжь
swearing something I’m fine Yes let’s
что-то матюкается Я нормально Да давай
fine of course yes I’m from the city of
нормально конечно да я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from Tuapse  Tuapse is the
Хмельницкий Вы откуда Туапсе туапс это
Krasnodar region
Краснодарский край
Dada Circassians Armenians who are you Circassians
Дада черкесы армяне кто вы черкесы
Circassians by Yes because usually Well, many
черкесы по Да потому что обычно Ну много
people from Russia don’t even know that
кто из России даже не знает что там
Tuapse Adler is there, all these places are
Туапсе Адлер вот эти все места это
Circassian lands it was then Russia
черкесские земли было это потом Россия
for the cut Yes, so what are
за порежь Да так что а чём общаетесь тут
we just communicating with here?  so you know, we spend time
мы просто так знаешь врем Время тратим
without being rude, we calmly communicate with people, I
не грубим спокойно общаемся с людьми
understand And you yourself are Circassians who come from the KBR
понял А вы сами черкесы родом там из КБР
gays
геи
Koro Black Sea
коро Черноморский
Cherke Shapsugs I understand I understand how, uh, you
черке шапсуги понял Понял а как ээ у вас
have a memory uh of those events there, the
вот есть память э о тех событиях там
Circassian genocide because I know that in
геноцид черкеса потому что я знаю что в
Kocha yes  yes, on May 21, the genocide of the Circassian
коча да да 21 мая геноцид черкесского
people in the Russian-Caucasian war, but
народа в русско-кавказская войне а
because I know that in this, in Chaev’s
потому что я знаю что в этом в ээ Чаева
Circassia, a procession was made
Черкесии шествие делали
for this day, also with the flags of Circassia. Well,
к этому дню тоже с флагами Черкесии Ну
Kabardians are doing Kabardians are doing
кабардинцы дела кабардинцы дела
Kabardians Yes yes yes also yes in short
кабардинцы Да да да тоже да короча
Circassia Cherke in short They are more
Черкесии черке короча Они они более
belong to the Turks, the Turks, the Turks, the
относятся к туркам тюркам тюркам тюркам
Turks, Yes, Ponya, the Turks, maybe, and the city of Cherkessk is
Да Поня тюркам может а город Черкеск это
in
в
which Cordi Karachevo Cherkessk There
какой корди карачево черкес Вот это в
was a demonstration in Cherkessk Well, now I’ll
Черкесске была демонстрация Ну сейчас я
look, Yes, there
посмотрю Да вот митинг да в Черкесске
was a rally in Cherkessk, well, in Cherkessk too Well, the Kabardians
был ну в Черкесске тоже Ну и кабардинцы
and well, the Circassians live Well, the Adyghe are Balkars
и ну черкесы живут Ну адыгейцы балкарцы
there is Nuno, this is already Kabardino Balkaria There
есть нуно это уже Кабардино Балкария Там
they are Balkars Well, they have a different language,
балкарцы они Ну это у них другой язык
they seem to have little relation to us, many
они к нам как бы мало отно у нас много
times we have different varieties of these languages, dialects,
раз разновидности этих языков диалекты
and not the Duma didn’t think that, for
разные а не Дума не думали что вот
example, in the future there might be like an
например в будущем может быть типа
independent Circassia Yes And here you are
независимая Черкесия Да И вот вы
It turns out that you will be a tourist
получается будете ну туристическим
region as well. How is some Slovenia?
регионом также Как там какие-то Словения
Yes, there is
Да там
Macedonia,
Македония
Greece, I don’t even know how to answer this
Греция даже не знаю как ответить на этот
question. Honestly, we didn’t think, I understood, yes, if
вопрос Честно не думали понял да на Если
only our genocide would be recognized, our
бы хотя бы наш геноцид признали бы наш
genocide is not recognized, you know, yeah
геноцид не признают понимаешь
I saw I saw something wrong  that they don’t
угу Я видел я видел не то что не
recognize I saw, in short,
признают Я видел короче парнишка
some guy, he came to a conference there,
какой-то он там приехал на конференцию
too, in some city, uh, in Kabardino
тоже в какой-то город э в Кабардино
Balka Yes, in Nalchik, and there were hanging these uh, with
балка Да в Нальчик и там висели эти э с
Ermolov bigboards, bigboards with Ermolov
ермоловы бигборды бигборды с ермоловы
type A Ermolov, he’s like, well, he
типа А Ермолов Он же типа как раз Ну
was in charge.  these genocides like e and Well, yes,
заведовал вот этими геноцидом типа е и
Ermolov is constantly singing for us Yes, and
Ну да Ермолов за нас ёт постоянно Да и
he’s like, damn, what is this
он такой типа говорит блин что это такое
here, well, as if instead of recognizing the
тут ну как бы вместо того чтобы признать
type of genocide, also like putting up
типа геноцид ещё типа развешать там
advertisements with this Ermolov
рекламу с этим ермоловы
Yes there is such a thing Yes there was such a thing I saw
Да есть такое Да было такое Я видел
Ermolov wait  Ermolov, on the contrary, the
Ермолов подожди Ермолов он же наоборот
estimate is still no, well, well,
смета всё нет ну то ж о он Вот как раз
he was just killing like, well, he was in command, he
он убивал типа ну то что он командовал
was killing from the Circassians Ermolov, he was going
он убивал от черкесов Ермолов он шёл
Ermolov, he, he, on the contrary, killed everyone with
Ермолов он он он наоборот всех убивал с
metal Yes, yes, yes, he killed all the Circassians, yes, but
метал Да да да черкесов всех убивал да А
I read
я читал же
this Yes Ermolov, on the contrary, he went
эту Да Ермолов наоборот он шёл всё ну
on the contrary, he massacred our people and uh
наоборот вырезал он наш народ причём э
Many even Russians don’t know that now, for
Многие даже россияне не знают что сейчас
example, in Turkey, there are more Circassians living
например в Турции да больше черкесов жит
than in Russia, although
чем в России хотя у
you have your own there, these
вас жит у них свои там эти
iodas in Israel, Palestine is also there a lot
иода в Израиле Палестина тоже там куча
because  then it was all the Ottoman
потому что тогда это было всё Османская
Empire Yes, and when they fled from the
империя Да и они когда бежали от
genocide they settled throughout the
геноцида они расселялись по всей
Ottoman Empire then it was
Османской империи тогда было
Yes, now it turns out If I’m not mistaken, in my
Да сечас получается Если я не ошибаюсь
opinion there are about a million Circassians in
то по-моему около миллиона черкесов
Turkey,
Турции
it turns out that in Russia there are several
сейс получается Росии там несколько
tens of thousands yes But in Turkey Yes from  d
десятков тысяч да А вот в Турции Да от д
to 3 Milonov, I say there more
до 3 Милонов я же говорю там больше
Yes, they have their own diaspora
Да там у них своя диаспора
now, well, the Circassian diaspora in Jordan,
сейчас ну Черкесская диаспора в Иордании
they generally have this king to guard or
у них вообще этот короля охранять или
whoever it is Circassian Guard Yes, yes, yes, they
кого там Черкесская гвардия Да да да
have a guard, he doesn’t trust anyone
гвардия у них есть он никому не доверяет
except
кроме
ours, I understand it’s interesting, yes that’s also  like the
наших понял интересно да это также как у
Pope or who had the
папы римской или у кого там была
Swiss Guard there once upon a time, well, they
швейцарская гвардия когда-то там ну
took it, they took it like they weren’t their own so that
брали брали типа не своих чтобы типа не
there weren’t some kind of conspiracies, not a king
было заговоров каких-то там да не короля
in Jordan, but a prince of some kind of security, in
в иордани а принца какого-то охрана
principle there was a prince Yes, I’m
принципе там прин Да я
interested, yes I understand  Maybe you have some
вот интересно да понял у вас Может какие
Questions
Вопрос
yes no I do
есть да нет не
n’t understand And you Stream Yes you do Yes yes I
не понял А ты Стрим Да ведёшь Да да я
stream I’m a Streamer from Ukraine but I
стримлю я Стример из Украины но я так
try so hard not to swear I try to
типа стараюсь не ругаться стараюсь так
conduct conversations so calmly yes correctly But the
спокойно разговоры вести да правильно А
point is and it’s mostly youngsters
смысл и это в основном малолетки что-то
starting something there  hoe something there it’s
начинают там тяпка что-то там это
not relevant at all Well, just if
неактуально на само де Ну просто если
a person speaks well Why w I I I I
человек хорошо разговаривать Почему ш я
once asked too there was a
я я я когда-то ещё спрашивал тоже был
guy uh
парень
he came across to me now I’ll tell you where uh
ээ он мне попадался сейчас скажу откуда
damn I don’t remember he’s also from some
э блин не вспомню он тоже из какой-то
Caucasian Republic I  I also asked
кавказской Республики Я тоже спрашивал
like, uh, if for example, your
вот типа э если например вот ваша
republic wants to become independent there,
республика захочет там стать независимой
and he says, damn, we won’t survive
и он говори блин так мы же не выживем
without Moscow. I say, damn, You
без Москвы Я говорю блин У вас курорты
get resorts. How much money does Turkey
получается Сколько денег да Турция
get on vacation? Yes How much money, like?
получает на отдыхе Да Сколько денег типа
Everything is shorter where there is a sea
Все короче там где есть море там бедно
no one will live in poverty there,
точно жить не будет никто
damn it, yes And the money goes to Moscow like this Well,
Блин да А деньги уходят в Москву вот так
what's up? Yes, everything flies there
Ну что дела Да всё туда летит
and Moscow builds, so the most interesting thing
б и Москва строит зна самое интересное
turns out to be Moscow Bert, uh, sort of
получается Москва Берт э-э как бы
takes away diamonds from the Yakuts Yes, the Tatars have
забирает там у якутов алмазы Да у татар
Bashkortos for oil  You, too, have all these
башкорто в нефть у вас вот тоже все эти
natural resources Yes, and Moscow, after all,
природные ресурсы Да и Москва все жи у
they have oil, these cost the same Bash NEF Yes
них же нефтяные эти стоят же Баш НЕФ Да
Bash of oil, like, damn, and a poor region,
Баш нефти типа ну блин и бедный регион
how can it be, yes, they steal because
как как может быть да воруют потому что
everything is like that, that’s also how it turns out for
всё да так та также типа получается у
you, like, well, uh  the region is rich in itself and a
вас типа ну э регион богатый сам по себе
huge number of
да приезжает огромное количество
tourists come, it’s just huge, almost
туристов просто Огромно чуть ли не там
all of Russia comes there, and
вся Россия ти приезжает Да и
what’s leaving and they supplied palaces there.
что уезжает а дворцы там поставляли
Like, we get pennies here, we
Типа а мы здесь копейки
work for them, we
получаем работаем на них копейки
get pennies for a month, even what month 3
получаем чтобы месяц даже какой месяц 3
days our salary is leaving because  that
дня наша зарплата Уходит потому что у
our prices here are such
нас здесь цены такие
damn, the salaries are meager in general and they are the ones who
блин зарплаты мизерные вообще и это они
will probably come there, like he
прит наверно там приедет там типа себя
almost thinks of himself as KLM Come on here
считает чуть ли не КЛМ Давай тут меня
Serving me Yes, probably in
Обслуживаю Да такое есть наверное у
Moscow we have such orders We immediately
москви мы таких наказы Мы таких сразу
punish such people correctly Well there is if
Наказываем правильно нема Ну есть если
you came Well  you have to treat people Well,
ты приехал Ну надо относиться Ну к людям
firstly, you’re on someone else’s territory, yes And
во-первых ты на чужой территории да А
secondly, you have to treat people they
во-вторых ты к людям должен относиться
serve you Not because
они тебя обслуживают Не потому что там
you’re a king there, like, but because, well, somewhere you
ты король типа а потому что ну где-то ты
served someone, now they’re serving you
кого-то обслужи теперь тебя обслуживают
Everyone does what  something like a function, some kind of
Каждый делает какую-то функцию какую-то
work This is not
работу Это не
all that there are some of these non-
все которые бы есть некоторые вот эти не
countries, here are the corners of Russia
страны вот уголки России приезжают
that come that I paid 500 rubles you
которые вот я заплатил 500 руб вы мне
owe me 1000 rubles I
должны 1000 руб
understand These are the ones that need to be put
понимаю Именно их таких надо ставить
Immediately in place then when they
Сразу на место потом они когда на
come next year they  they are already thinking about
следующий год приезжают они уже думают о
what to talk about, how to behave,
чём разговаривать как себя
so it happens, they come there to the
таква так бывает приезжают там вот на то
same sea, there they drink bottles, they throw
же море там бухают бутылки там швыряют
whatever you want, they do it there, well, that’s our kind, well,
всё что хочешь делают там ну это наше
we paid for it, like, well, there’s
типа Ну мы же за это заплатили типа ну а
no mentality. Well, no, I don’t care about the local
никакого и менталитета Ну нету к местным
people  if they have
людям пофиг им если если у них есть
money, then they are Kings, we get
бабки значит они Короли мы получаем
pennies, they come for our money, they
копейки они приходят за наши же бабки
get high here, brawlers, whatever you want, if
здесь кайфуют дебошир всё что хочешь
you touch them with a finger, they immediately run to the police
пальцем их тронешь сразу бегут в полицию
and, well, write off a statement or so on,
и ну спишут заявление или или так далее
and they consider themselves
и они считают себя
right, you just see in Turkey  easier
правыми просто вот видишь в Турции проще
Turkey is an independent state Yes, and there
Турция независимое государство Да и там
you come, yes Well, for example, if
вот ты приезжаешь да Ну например если
someone from Russia is rowdy there Yes, he was
кто-то из России там буянит Да его без
evicted from the hotel without any problems to the police, everyone
проблем из отеля выселили в полицию всё
was deported back and that’s it And no one
депортировали назад и всё И никто не
stands on ceremony calmly without any yes yes yes
церемонится спокойно без всяких да да да
And like And here he is  it starts with me I'm from
И типа А тут он начинает это я Я с
Moscow there, in short, what did you tell me they,
Москвы там короче что ты мне расска они
they also consider you know everyone else, they're
е они ещё считают знаешь всех других это
second-class people, even Those who are from
людьми второго сорта даже Те кто с
St. Petersburg, here in Moscow, they're like that, damn it
Питера вот Москва они такие вот он блин
Himself Maybe there He moved from some damn
Сам Может быть там Переехал из какой-то
Klyazma, in short, to Moscow  He’s already lived for a year
блин Клязьмы короче в Москву год уже
and he’s already a Muscovite, like there are those,
пожил и всё он уже Москвич типа те такой
and that’s how he comes to us. Yes,
есть есть да вот так же к нам вот
to an aul somewhere there,
приезжает Да в аул там куда-нибудь там
from the same Moscow, they’ll buy a
вот из той же Москвы там купят там
plot of land there, they’ll build a house, your
участок нахуй построят дом у вас говорит
dog says, your dog barks.
собака говорит лает у вас собака лает у
Your chickens are barking, there's a crowing, this is my land,
вас курочки там кукарека это моя земля
some kind of your Earth. Damn, what they're building is what
какая-то ваша Земля Чер надо их то что
they
они
're building, like what they're doing, well, they're making
строит типа что они получается ну делают
a house, it'll also excite that you have, in short,
дом ещё возбудит что у вас короче
living creatures like, yes, like, yes, they'll come from
живность типа да типа да вот приедут
God knows where, from Moscow there.
чёрт знает откуда вот там с Москвы там
Well, basically, near Moscow, they
вот ну в основном под Москвой вот вот
’ll buy this plot of land, set up workshops,
это купят участок ставят цехи всё что
do whatever they want, and they’re hampered by the fact that there’s a
хотят делают и им мешает то что там
dog barking there, a chicken, a cow,
собачка гавкает там курочка корова
you’re here and from time immemorial you’ve lived on your own
чи вы тут и спокон веков жили на своих
lands, you’re living here, they’re running a farm, they’re
землях тут живёте ведёте хозяйство они
Yes, that’s a joke, of course.
Да это конечно прикол
Okay brother, Let’s go  yes let's good all
Ладно брат Пойдём мы да давай хорошо всё
the best all the best let's all the
хорошего всё давай всего
best Circassia will be
хорошего Черкесия будет
free so squeak like comment write to
свободно так писка лайк комент пись на
my Telegram right now axis VN and
мий Telegram прям зараз ось ВН а
Popik is more and more respectful YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
keeping us busy through srg Orcs your ban and even
заня нас через срг Орки твый бан и дуже
more video I don’t show people
багато видео не показую людям
often I don’t show information  about streaming
вчасно не показуе информация про стрими
Tom for this purpose, we need to write a Mali operational
Тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
link right away and while there in
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegra okm video schezh tsikava and
телегра окм видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we are responsible for you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
is independent in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
letter
пись
E
E